Once upon a time, there was a man who fell in love with a doll.
Perhaps the man's love made itself felt,
for one day the doll came to life and began to dance.
The man was delighted.
He thought a doll would never betray his love,
and that now he could have the world's most pure and innocent love all to himself.
Unfortunately for him, the doll who had been given life
rejected the man's love and fell in love with another man.
Oh, I couldn't sleep.
Muto.
I wonder why he did that.
For him to jump out of the window like that,
could it be because his heart hasn't been completely returned yet?
Then I've got to try even harder to get the rest of his heart back for him
and do it quickly.
What the hell happened?
Muto has called into the office!
No way!
Oh, must be for the pushing incident.
Huh?
Pushing in?
You don't know, Doc.
The wonderful Fakir pushed the wonderful and unresisting Muto out of the window.
What?
There's got to be some kind of mistake because Muto jumped out himself.
It wasn't as if he'd do that.
Everyone was watching, so excuses won't work.
But it...
That was just too cruel, even for Fakir.
Oh, I hope he becomes a full-fledged criminal and plunges headlong down the path to becoming one of life's losers.
Anyway, let's go see!
Yes, let's!
But when I saw him, I'm sure that he...
That was simply due to my carelessness.
Unpleasant incidents just keep happening lately, don't they?
What exactly happened yesterday?
That was simply due to my carelessness.
What?
Just an accident.
Accident?
Yes.
I'm sorry to have caused you worry.
Why would you lie like that?
What do you mean, Mr. Fakir?
I must say, I am reluctant to accept the accident explanation myself.
Are you saying you believe that Fakir pushed me out of the window, Mr. Cat?
Arguments can sometimes happen, Mr. Muto.
For example, Albrecht and Hilarion both wanted to marry the maiden Giselle.
Their desire to marry her caused them to...
And ma...
I suppose you're a little...
I'm a little young for that particular problem.
Well, that's fine.
But I cannot let you continue to live in one room.
Then I will...
I will leave.
But here...
Ah!
Quite audacious of you to be eavesdropping on me.
Keep it up and I'll have you married!
Ah!
Those eyes again!
What's happened to you, Muto?
He looks like he's in pain.
Well, he was betrayed by the person he thought was his best friend.
Which he nearly covered for senior Fakir anyway.
That's who like him.
Who are you?
Who are you inside of me?
Who is he talking to?
Oh!
P.K.?
Um, you know, this might be none of my business, but I think you're making a big mistake.
I'm talking about senior Fakir.
You two have been friends for a long time, so it's not that I don't understand why you'd
want a cover for him in front of Mr. Cat.
But if something like this happens a second time, you might end up never being able to
dance again, or worse.
Why are you talking to me about this?
Uh, yesterday I saw you.
I saw you gliding down from the sky with this enormous white bird next to you.
When I saw that, I thought maybe you were being protected by, like, the god of death or something.
White bird?
Does she mean Tutu?
You say such cute things, P.K., and you have a forthright, steadfast, and beautiful heart
beating within you.
Excuse me, I have to go.
P.K.?
I saw that.
What?
He's gone.
A crow's feather?
Is this?
I know.
I'll go talk to Fakir.
Anyway, I have to turn back into a girl somewhere.
No good.
Too many people.
I got it.
This place should be okay.
Man, I really danced my butt off.
Uh-oh.
Where did Dylan go?
Mr. Armadellon!
Yes, sir.
Doopee, doopee.
He scared me.
Wait, there's no time for worrying.
I wonder where Fakir is.
Uh-oh.
Hey, is something going on with him?
With Fakir.
He's acting weird.
He's up in the library.
Hold up in there.
Library?
He's really here.
Hey, Fakir.
Just now, Muto and P.K.,
and it was really weird.
And Muto was...
And what happened yesterday was weird, too.
And I thought Mowzinski's shoes might be Muto's fault,
but that could just be my imagination.
But, but, but, it really was super weird,
so Muto is...
Can you please be a little quieter?
No!
I'm sorry.
Calm down.
Did something happen to Muto?
That's what I'm trying to find out.
And what happened yesterday?
Muto jumped out the window himself, didn't he?
But in front of Mr. Cat,
he made it sound like he was just covering for you.
And that made it look like you were the bad guy.
Oh, and just now,
I was following Muto around to see what was up,
and then he vanished all of a sudden.
He left behind...
a crow's feather.
What?
Oh!
Why did you stop?
It's Rue!
Vakir?
Vakir!
You did this.
What did you do to Muto?
What do you mean?
Don't play dumb with me!
Let go of me!
That hurts!
Show your true colors!
Cree!
Stop it!
Let go of me!
Don't worry about me.
I'll be just fine so like Muto. He's incredibly mature. As much as Fakir's immature
Oh
Duck's prince is changing and not for the better. I'm afraid
Do something fast little duck before the beautiful sparkle in the eyes under that evil mask fades completely
Are you in pain father?
I want to leave this place as soon as I can if I were free
I could wrap these wings around my dear daughter and hug her as much as I wanted you only need endure it a little longer father
It looks like the prince has found us our prey
The princess
Oh
I'm so glad I obeyed your instructions father
Yes
If I had not soaked the heart shard with a feeling of love in father's blood that day like he told me to
My prince would not have returned to me
I
Have to be grateful to princess tutu for giving the heart shard back to him
It would serve you well also to be accommodating to princess tutu
In order to break the seal to release me we have to find the rest of the prince's heart shards
We need princess tutu's power to do that if you try to get rid of her again
I'll show you no mercy daughter or not
I'm sorry I won't father
Good
Hey there man
Other than myself
No one but the prince in the story can truly love a pitiful person like you
Who despite being a crow have been born into this hideous human body
I am sure we would both like to see your wedding day as soon as possible
Thank you father
I feel like that day was such a long time ago
Duck
Happy news
Oh what?
Well I just heard starting tomorrow the wonderful Fakir is suspended from school for a whole week
No way
Yes way
At this rate he'll graduate from juvie to felon in no time
Fakir was
More importantly
Just now while I just happened to be following PK
I just happened to see her meet up with Mewto
And as I just happened to keep following them
They went off to a place where there was absolutely no one around
Pk was with Mewto
Well when I just happened to go see
That's a pirate
Pirate
See?
Pk
Hey hold on
Duck what?
What are you doing?
Um uh you see?
What's wrong?
You have a problem with this?
Just what do you care if Mewto and I are dating?
That's our business
What?
Mewto you like Pk?
Those eyes again
Mewto what's happened to you?
Something's weird here
What's so weird about going out with me?
No that's not what I meant
I meant yesterday and stuff
Mewto jumped out the window himself
But you're still saying that?
And Mr. Cat's shoes
Mewto might be
Would you cut it out already?
Mewto
Just who are you?
What are you trying to make me do?
Mewto wait
Stay away
Mewto why?
Aw it was just getting good too
Hey Pk please come out
Let's take this outside right now
We can talk peacefully okay?
We're gonna straighten a few things out
I'm sorry but be quiet for a second
Huh?
But you have to take a harsher tone with your enemies
Lillie I don't think of Pk as an enemy
Really?
Doug?
Is this really okay?
Uh huh
That's how I feel
Hey!
She says as an enemy
You're not worth thinking about
That isn't what I meant
That's enough for today
Let's go
I'll let you open this for today
Mewto?
That's enough for today
Let's go
I'll let you open this for today
Mewto?
You're working intently
Is the subject of your research princes?
Or is it ravens?
Shall I tell you what the prince is moving towards becoming?
So you did do something
The hard shard of love that princess Tutu gave back to him?
That shard was soaked in a bath of the ravens blood so
The ravens blood?
Then you
My father was willing to part with some of his own blood for the sake of his daughter
The ravens daughter?
The prince will soon change
He'll love only me
And he'll find a young and beautiful heart for my father and offer it up to him as a sacrifice
When the blood has finished permeating his whole heart, he will never go back to the way he was
Did you tell Tutu about all this?
I should
If I did that, I could make her suffer, couldn't I?
Or perhaps
It would be more effective to tell the prince that she is in truth a girl who is really a wretched excuse for a dancer
It was stupid of you to break the prince's sword
Without that blade, you can't even hope to take his heart out now, can you?
But you're only human after all
Maybe all you can do is look things up in books
Pique
Sorry about before
I truly and honestly need your love
Alright
Are you afraid?
No, of course not
Pique, promise to love only me
Alright
Promise me that you'll hate everyone else
I will
I promise to love only you
And to hate everyone else too
Pique
Alright
As proof then
You'll give me your beautiful heart
Won't you?
Yes
Then step forward
Into my arms
Give me your heart
That's the Waltz of the Doll
It's from Capella
If I can just have Mewtwo
I don't mind losing my heart and turning into a doll
The more beautiful the heart,
the stronger the fragrance when it's dyed in evil.
Didn't Muto fall in love with Pique?
No, he mustn't take Pique's heart!
Wait, please come dance with me.
Won't you, Pique?
No.
Tutu!
Pique!
Your pleas are useless.
Pique herself wants to give her heart to me
and become a sacrifice.
As long as her feelings stay this way.
Pique, stop!
Is this truly what you desire?
Swanilda from Capellia was a normal girl
merely pretending to be a doll.
Just like you, Pique.
A girl who likes chatting,
singing and loves dancing.
A girl deeply in love.
If you really love Muto,
then you must want to chat with him
and sing and dance with him, right?
You say you don't mind losing your heart,
but that's not the real you!
Oh no!
Ah!
Tutu!
Muto...
Is this all a bad dream?
What?
Another me inside me is due to what's going to happen to me.
I...
Mewtwo.
Good morning, princesses.
Hey, what happened?
Oh, you don't remember?
Duck dragged you home late last night and put you into bed.
Um...
The two of you must have had a magnificent, spectacular battle.
Oh, how I wish I'd seen it!
Both of you abandoning friendship to fight!
Two girls in love with Mewtwo!
Me in love with Mewtwo?
Oh, yeah. Come to think of it, I guess I was, huh?
BK, thank goodness.
So, how'd you two fight?
We did it!
What? You gotta be kidding me!
But, man, to be honest, I don't even know myself why I was so crazy about Mewtwo in the first place.
Oh, that must be what you call the rashness of youth.
I'm sticking to Fakir love from now on!
Princess Tutu is the only one who can get back the princess' heart.
But who can turn the heart soaked in Raven's blood back to normal?
Will Princess Tutu be able to do that?
Is there something happening behind the scenes where I can't see it?
I don't want to fight anymore.
It would be wonderful if the world were full of flowers, wouldn't it?
Your beautiful heart makes beautiful flowers bloom.
I was looking for a tail and I found her in Batzora!
Well, her name is Uzura.
Karin made her from the wood from Edel that didn't burn up.
Rehi, what have you done to Muto?
The one who made the prince like this is you, Tutu.
Why? Why won't you love me?
All you children who love stories, come gather round!
.
sa